a piece of paradise
with brownie inside
and that's my bro brand packaging
I want people to understand that my brand
she has history
I'm pasting it on the label that my brother was a artist
Charlie Brown's
Brazil doesn't want to take this one from the series
I think it was Charlie Brown's first show
I'm here
oh here we are at a show with Marcelo d dos
cry part two
here I too am painting the one with the white cap
cry singing there ó
that's it brother
satisfaction
I will make our stop here first
if we deliver the product into someone's hand
the guy will notice that Charlie Brown
he will
it's a skate wheel
was made by a
by an artist
the man lived
lived
with history you give me this honor to do
to be able to make this stop
I show you there
good
I already make this idea today
so what did i think of a guy like that
end we started with this here
how i created this whole skateboard wheel concept
i remember the cray wheel
or those flashier wheels
so if you get a shock pink
she has one more connotation to see
not with a cut chocolate thing
what will happen
we are going to make a pink chocolate
the bearing is pink
turned on
has brownie you don't have an edible skateboard wheel
has I brought you
o
iPad turns her already
I managed to do the things I want manually
so I'm going to start this construction now all separated
ah
just to let you know that my partner had a package rolled
continues
what's left of time
and this is what we will rotate from now on
a brand is nothing without history bro
we are together we go there